episode where I cover three things, what's on my mind this week. Recommended reading
this week's curation gets you thinking about your own systems. Before you close the
laptop for the weekend, I'm your host, Joe Casabona, and here's what's on my mind
For August 7th, 2026,
first on my mind resetting Claude, every three months my friend Doc Rock sent me
an interview with Boris Cherney, who's the head of Claude Code last week while I
was on vacation. And the advice struck me.
Cherney basically says we should reset our prompts, projects, skills every time there's
a new model.
while my estimation after a couple of listens is he's largely talking about Claude
don't like this at all.
One of the reasons I try to stick with one model nay, one
But this is also why I always say we don't hire large language models. Imagine if
you hired someone and then they got that men in black flashy thingy thing every three
months and their memory was wiped.
Kay, have you ever flashy thing me? No, I ain't playing with you, Kay. Have you ever
flashy thing me? No.
I am not going to reset the memory. I'm going to keep my simple set of directives
and if the large language model gets worse at doing that task, I'll just do the task
myself.
This is something that you generally don't need to worry about with Zapier or make
or shortcuts.
The technical debt seems to accumulate much, much faster with large language models
because they're evolving so quickly. So my question for you is, is the time
it saves you worth having to reset or retrain your large language model every quarter?
The discovery of it doing the job worse when you expect it to be consistent?
Is it worth it in these cases? Or maybe a bigger question is, are you even checking
the work of the large language model? 'cause this is something that you need to do
we should also trust that our employees or contractors are not going to dramatically
change
multiple times per year.
So I'd love to know what you think of this. Do you have something on your mind? How
Okay, so for recommended Reading Destiny of the Republic by Candace Millard,
this is a book that I finished while I was on vacation and thoroughly enjoyed it.
I know shockingly, or maybe not shockingly little about James Garfield. I said this
to my father-in-law and he goes, most people don't know anything about James Garfield.
and he's like a history buff. So,
I, I know shockingly little about James Garfield, for example, he was a congressman
who left his post to fight in the Civil War and did very well at that. He was nominated
for president despite vehemently protesting it. He did not want this job,
and he was one of four presidents assassinated in office.
Destiny of the Republic is Garfield story, but it's also one of mental health and
access. People had to presidents until the early 20th century.
People could just walk in to the president. They had like open calling hours or open
office hours multiple times per week.
it's a sort of access that members of the press barely get today.
It's also a story of technology and evolution of medicine.
Alexander Graham Bell is heavily featured in this book as well, and I learned a ton
about him.
This is the second book I've read from Candace Millard. I've got it right here on
my desk. Destiny of the Republic by Candace Millard.
And I love her style.
She's a fantastic storyteller and the way she weaves a story together to keep it
interesting without it being histrionic is excellent. I highly recommend it. It's
also,
uh, the book is the inspiration for the Netflix series, death by Lightning, which
has one of my favorite actors Nick Offerman in it. So I highly recommend this book.
I'm even more excited to watch this series now.
Okay, moving on to something fun or maybe just something interesting. And so I think
this week's recommended reading was, is a fun one,
walking Without Headphones. This is my first week back from vacation and one of my
favorite things to do
on vacation is take a walk before the rest of the house wakes up. I'm often the first
one up anyway, but my kids, especially my oldest, are starting to rival that
thoughts instead of having to fill every silence. And while the walks with my daughter
were not filled with silence, something I happily subbed for daddy-daughter time.
My walks at home have been, I've continued the habit by walking one to one and a
quarter miles every morning
with nothing but my watch. I it, it's been nice, it's been nice listening to the
sounds of the town where I live and not have something filling my brain, letting
my mind
wander, letting myself be present
taking a walk without your headphones or just sitting in silence.
It's something that we don't do enough of these days.
Okay, so there is no automation of the week this week, but I do have a quick promo
if you want to learn more,
SHO in Philly in September.
Sho is setting sale this September and I am
honored to be a captain this year. In my session, you'll learn how to create a framework
that sets boundaries and resets expectations in your inbox.
Join us for two days of deep discussion, connection, and fun.
As we pave the future of operations work.
Grab your ticket@processdriven.co slash ahoy.
That's process driven.co/a
But that's it for this episode of the Friday wrap up. These episodes are about taking
more time off, especially on the weekends, and the best way you can do that is by
having a good system. If you are not sure where to start, head over to streamlined
fm slash quiz, answer a few questions and I'll send you exactly where you should
start to build a less overwhelming business.